<item>
<question>
What is the output of the following?
A = [1,2,3,4]
B[0] = 5
print A
</question>
<answer>
[5, 2, 3, 4]
</answer>
</item>
<item>
<question>
Is string mutable?
</question>
<answer>
Yes. It means that everytime you do something like:
a='apple'
The object representing 'apple' cannot be modified in memory even when you call methods on the object. Contrast this with lists s.a. [1].append(2)
</answer>
</item>

<question>
Explain copy, deep copy and assignment
</question>
<answer>
Ask the trainer dude. He should be explaining it
</answer>
<question>
Ternary operator (a?b:c in other languages) - how does it look like in Python?
</question>
<answer>
a=b if c else d
</answer>
<question>
What is the o/p?
a="ba"
print a*2
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
Is this valid? 
a<b == c
</question>
<answer>
Yes. It represents the condition: (a less than b) and (b equals c)
</answer>
<question>
print set(1,2,3)  | set(2,3,4)
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
Functions and ints are objects in Python, true or false?
</question>
<answer>
True
</answer>
<question>
A function with a generator has: the yield keyword, the generate keyword or the raise keyword?
</question>
<answer>
yield
</answer>
<question>
Apart from __next__ we need a ____ function to implement an iterator
</question>
<answer>
__iter__
</answer>
<question>
The computational complexity of slicing k characters from a string of length n is (mystr[p:q]) ? O(n), O(nlogk) O(k)
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
What keyword do we use to define a function in Python?
<question>
<answer>
def
</answer>
<question>What's the Python philosophy? There is only one obvious way to do something OR there are many ways to do something and you choose what you want
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
How old is Guido Van Rossum?
</question>
<answer>
Wikipedia
</answer>
<question>
How old are you? 
</question>
<answer>
Your adhaar card has it
</answer>
<question>
Did Shaktimaan kill Kilvish?
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
To convert a string into an int we do: parseint('123'), int('123'), '123'.int()
</question>
<answer>
int('123')
</answer>
<question>
Whats the difference between assignment and copy ?
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
To use the function ceil from module math, which one should you prefer? import math OR from math import ceil
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
The default case for a switch statement in Python is At the Beginning OR at the end?
</question>
<answer>
<answer>
<question>
a=b if c else d is an example of Relational Operator, Conditional Operator, jump statement?
</question>
<answer></answer>
<question>
which keyword is used to subclass a class in Python? inherits/extends
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
'a' is a character and "a" is a string?
</question>
<answer>
</answer>
<question>
What is your name ? 
</question>
<answer>
I have no fucking idea
</answer>
